gemzies.com 2008-12-22

# Gemzies Terms and Conditions

## Gemzies PRIVACY POLICY

The Gemzies website (the "Gemzies Site") is offered to you by Gemzies B.V. By using the Gemzies Site, you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

### What information do we collect?

When you visit our web site (the "Gemzies Site"), you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose and that is collected on an individual basis, and web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse through the Gemzies Site. 

When you register at the Gemzies Site or provide feedback to us by using contact forms or messages, you provide us with information about yourself, including your email address. If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. 

Other users of the Gemzies Site may view your user profile information that is published on the Gemzies Site, and will be able to track all postings made by you on the Gemzies Site by using the bookmark feature. You can choose to show your contact information to any visitor of the Gemzies Site together with your profile information. If you choose this option, other users will be able to contact you using the contact information as shown. 

### Purposes of processing

We collect and process information about users and visitors to the Gemzies Site to make available our services, to make it possible for users to contact each other (provided you have chosen to show your contact information to other users), to inform users about any changes and for the development of web statistics and further improvement of our services. 

The information you provide may be used to contact you when necessary, e.g. to notify you about functionality changes to the Gemzies Site, the services, the Terms of Use or this Privacy Policy. If you have chosen to show your contact information to other users, this contact information may also be used by other users of the Gemzies Site to contact you. 

### Cookies

We may use small text files called cookies and web server logs to collect information about how the Gemzies Site is used. Information gathered through cookies and web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at the Gemzies Site, and the web sites visited just before and just after you have visited the Gemzies Site. 

Cookies help us make the Gemzies Site easier to use by not requiring you to log in each time you visit the Gemzies Site, by remembering which pages within the Gemzies Site are your favorites, etc. We may use cookies or web server logs to help track or diagnose problems on the Gemzies Site, improve performance, or to disable accounts that are in violation of our Terms of Use. 

You can disable cookies by changing the settings of your browser but we do not recommend this as you will not be able to use many of the features and the services offered at the Gemzies Site. Specific settings regarding cookies depend on the type of browser. 

### Your ability to edit and delete your account information

You can edit your account information, including your profile and contact information settings, at any time. If you wish to terminate your use of the Gemzies Site, you can delete your account at any time. 

### Third parties

We will not sell, rent or share identifiable personal information about our users to third parties, except:

  * In case of a business transfer. Should we enter into a business transaction that involves the buying or selling of assets, user information, including contact information such as email addresses, may be transferred per the transaction agreement. We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or any dissolution 
  * As required by law or to enforce the safety and security of the Gemzies Site, our members or employees.

### Third party sites

Gemzies by its nature includes links to many different web sites. We are not responsible for the practices employed by web sites linked to or from the Gemzies Site, nor the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from the Gemzies Site to another web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other web site, including web sites which have a link on the Gemzies Site, is subject to that web site's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding. 

### How to contact us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our data processing activities, you can contact us via email using: [feedback@gemzies.com](mailto:feedback@gemzies.com). 

### Amendments to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change this policy at any time. Changes will be posted on the Gemzies Site to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it.
